Open it up
loot loot
loot
[music]
Hello friends operators welcome back to 9
videos welcome to imposters just after
youtube channel how is the cost price how was
today the market hit a jackpot we will
talk about it in premium format
but at this time the company has posted excellent results
in ICICI Bank water for the most newly installed company
here
net profit increased by 60%
earned a tree of 7000 crores the company has
posted much better results than HDFC in every parameter ICICI Bank so is ICICI Bank going to be the
next HDFC Bank so
for this there are complete charts to find out
we will give you complete address I will give you
price 4 of the next that targets are being
closed here in the short term
what price target will you
see eyebrow yes there
is a lot of police on that here ICICI
Bank so we will talk in full details
and shock tomorrow how can ICICI Bank perform in intraday
I will
tell you complete details also pointed stocks of tomorrow
See the best levels of five Indian stocks, subscribe here
boss, whatever I said in the Friday session,
show it coming true here today, there was a
good fall in Nifty today, see here, let me
tell you that the fifth
internet stocks which I have picked for tomorrow, will
give you a lot of momentum in them, you
can call them, if you follow the labels
then proper labels map map and I will tell you the entry points,
so stay tuned to the video, here in the
Premium Plus group, today in the
morning I have updated,
see the exact same thing, I had
told in the Friday trading session that
SGX Nifty will reach 1649 on Monday,
then Nifty will also come down, so I made a profit
of 1200, you
can see from the line, more than 13 profit, this is
intraday profit, see here
in every line, it worked in 12 years and 12 lots,
those people also cleared a good profit
book, here someone's 12000, someone
's
67 thousand here  Some people get 3000, some people get
10000 rupees, some get 1000 rupees,
every single person has booked a good profit here, so this is
proper guidance, proper guidance
and proper guidance. The result of finding a one-stop solution here is that
we provide proper guidance
here.
All the members of the Premium Plus group
get proper guidance here that you have to
enter here, you have to set a
complete setup here. We hold your hand and tell you to
work at such a level only then you
can make a profit and we get you properly
entered. There was a star in proper profit, the
result of this is that you
can see every client here has made money today,
that this grain has a high profit,
so look here, if you join the
Premium Plus group, the slot that is vacant here right now,
that is of cost plus 7 days
extra, see for positive vibes, the
free premium job fee that is running right now, the
history is 1992, use demand everyday brother,
this prevent double line of yours gets booked
here in a single day, seven to eight thousand rupees here.
Bye bye minimum
capital of ten thousand, the one who has a
capital of ten thousand, he also made 8000 rupees today, so you
can understand how label matters work,
so whoever wants to join now,
kindly confirm the payment screenshot by WhatsApping
this on Telegram
in the description, I am mentioning the number in the pin comment
9807 5711, that is the number
of prostate, please send this screenshot by WhatsApping this on Telegram,
Highway ji, I will add you immediately
after 10 successful payment screenshots
here, then
in the Mosted Premium Plus group, where regularly
today also, as soon as the market opened,
I made a foot buy of 17200, the services
here were damaged and when the market opened, you
can see the rest of the Nifty 6000
bike was damaged, the goods here became 200 ₹15
in a few hours, so similar profits
here, he has also been gifted Dhindha
of 36,000, the food bike here was
clearly thirty  Sixth place is the major
distance from Bank Nifty. Keeping that in mind,
I placed a
put trade of 36,000 here.
We booked a good profit of 451, 350 as well. So, with such
proper guidance, if you want to
earn money regularly from the stock market, I am talking about serial status,
which looks at the market as a serious
business.
You want to earn money regularly in Nifty, Bank Nifty Equity, intraday. You want to develop a business model
and if you want to get rid of your job, then
join the Premium Plus group and earn
regularly from the market.
Here we promise that whatever you invest in
premium features will be
recovered in a single day. So it will work.
Moving ahead in this video, do subscribe here. Do
like Pandey's video and
I am going to tell you the result of ICICI Bank.
After the excellent hidden comments of the management, today ICICI Bank
again took control of Bank Nifty. I am
telling you again because those who
know and work in options.
After the quarterly results of ICICI Bank, Bank Nifty rose to 1301, so
despite the bad market today, you
can see that Bank Nifty handled the politics,
otherwise Nifty
was ready to go to 16700 today, but here ICICI
Bank posted good results and again
handled the bank, so what will be the next price
target, for that first you have to do the
celebs, it is best to just balance, if you
start now, then I will also
explain the edit to you with the help of stocks,
so whoever has belief in this, who wants to invest
in the market by mixing it with himself,
that this is the
best app for yoga,
download the TikTok app here, the PIN has been shared in the office,
first verify your email ID,
just use it here, I
am talking for new users on IMO Sunday,
then use it on Sunday, stop this premise
underlying free for you guys,
you do not need to write any debit card or credit card at all,
use it for one month,
if you find it useful then
also buy the premium paid subscription of TikTok  If you
can do this, then look at the stock here. If
I give you an update, then the
board here has appointed Mr.
Anil Da Banerjee as the Accredited Financial
Officer, which will come into effect from May 1st. So
after that, look at the quarters. Since yesterday,
we used to discuss the ICICI
Bank website, which counts Nifty, Bank Nifty,
and how great it is.
When the net profit of any bank
is searched here, after that we have a
good confidence of the bank. The
way the information is increasing here,
if the interest rate increases, the
bank will benefit the most. There are 19 parameters
which are coming out that it is much better than HDFC Bank. By the
numbers of ICICI Bank, here the brokerage house is
estimating that it can even surpass HDFC Bank.
So, ICICI Bank can be done
next to HDFC Bank in terms of
numbers and in terms of three 60% when the net
profit is searched here.  7000 crore
paste and you see
how dramatically the gross NPA of the company has come down,
you can see how good the gross NPA is
here, people can see the dance item, the
gross NPA has come down to 3.6
in the last quarter, if you
compare quarter to quarter, then it is quite good, don't
side almost point five three
almost five percent less, people can see the downside, the
gross NPA baby came to 0.76, so
from every parameter, the result of the company for the
quarter was half excellent here, that is why today
we saw that even today the
result of ICICI Bank has folded the Bank Nifty,
but for how long it can do so will
depend, there are charts in the form of touch tube,
I will explain to you what can happen in the short term and long term,
before that let's
understand a little fundamentals of the company, one and a half inch is quite
good, many brokerage houses like it,
I also like it personally, see the GPS here,
36 per cent, piece birth here, so
thirty six  With IPS, here the
company trades at 20.83 multiple,
which bank ICICI Bank practices only
trading 2030 multiple, so you see in both there is
absolutely steady growth, here it is
not like Adani Group stock where peer pressure is
₹500 and your GPS is at 0584, so it is
growing steadily, that means
ICICI Bank may still have police,
you can still see your labels,
some such brokerage houses have
vitamins of 9000, here this is, so here the
price to issue is just such a
quality stock, you were getting it at a price
to book multiple of just 2.94, it
is a very good stock, on this word you
should definitely do this combination, there are charts of ICICI Bank,
we
can see for this, ICICI Bank is at
760, if the stock goes above 0803, then
with a stop loss of 720,
you should look at the 0803 targets within exactly six months
According to this, the
FAT here will hike its rates,
RBI will also hike the rates here, otherwise
if there is no rate hike then
we cannot even get this information, so the
interest rate here will not increase, no matter how much the
interest rate hike will be
beneficial, so here ICICI
Bank can become the next HDFC Bank, it can
definitely become, in fact, they are telling the same thing
in the last two quarters, now see what
great returns UPS and P are getting, you are
ignoring so much study, the leadership inside the trophy is
straight at the price to book of 2.94,
so try to consolidate at this level,
760 will be the base zone, if it comes to 750 then
add 748 and add
721 here, but do place this trick stop loss,
for short-term basis I am telling you that the
first target of strength is
98030, you will see it within 6 to 9 months,
so definitely
ICICI Bank is at a very good
support zone here and see here
clearly  A support here indicates
that this stock is clearly a support. So,
if the stock does this despite the support, then at
least it can go up to Rs.1100. Let
me tell you clearly,
you will see this price target within six to nine months. In
fact, Nomura has also
given targets of Rs.1000 here.
Morgan Stanley has done a very good job.
Each and every brokerage house of
police in this stock, definitely buy it here. This regiment will make
you money even in such a bearish market.
So look here
for tomorrow, the first thing that will start is Rahul,
sell JSPL here. Jindal
Steel and Power, but look at 521,
understand the strategy first, then you
can enter. First of all, join my Freedle Gram channel.
You will find the link in the description. Whatever stocks I will tell you about in the video today,
tomorrow before the market
opens, you will get all the stocks with
proper leveling. All these
labels become very important for intraday. All those
interested readers who have Big Boss
level  You make money after working in discipline,
otherwise how will you
make money, there will be proper and proper labels,
entry will be at the right time, you will book this office properly,
it is not that you thought that you will make a profit of 12000,
otherwise you will make 18000, so
see this is not a gamble,
take it as a serious business, take it
regularly, today we have even
shown how to make money regularly, we are
making money regularly from the market,
see this result of today, 80 people book
in intraday, so take JSPL here,
take it on the labels here,
you have to select below 521,
stoploss of 525, 519, 517, 514, additionally
for this you have to do juice films, there is a
possibility of selling metal stocks getting a little more special here, second pick bill is
also for selling side and in Arvindo Pharma and
in Arvindo Pharma here between 635 to 615
you have to make more immense profit and stoploss of 641
For 632 6363 targets tomorrow you will have to sell in Apaar
and stay tuned to the video
here in the end I am going to tell you
how ICICI Bank can perform in Inter tomorrow
with proper level third of Basir
here I would like to get an update on BPCL,
crude oil price can decrease again tomorrow because
see here the
structure of IFFCO in Nifty Banquet, tell me
that is fine, see clearly for tomorrow if the
game download opens after breaking 1698 color feet then the
market can reach directly to 16700, so be
absolutely questionable here,
today's closing minimum was supposed to come above 17000, that is why
we would have taken a positive in the soil yesterday,
but because the
closing has come below 17000, then it is considered a living
psychological level and a pure support level
for the post riders, the entire
leaders here have been unwinding
from the position, the bank wall writing is being done by pressing
17000 feet, so  17000 will be the major
distance from this week, so
consider that as your stoploss. If both the sides below
are open till 16500, then this expiry can
also be of 16500, so the market can fall tomorrow as well, so keeping
that in mind,
crude oil can again run away from tomorrow, so you should
like it and it will be best to see if the
price goes up, then from here the oil
marketing companies benefit, so
take it at 370, you have to bike above 370,
stoploss of 365, 374, 376,
10:38 M gap of Bhavnagar, if there is any gap
in BPCL, then avoid that topic,
for spreading at all, do not work on the level,
you will definitely make money. Fourth, the
stuffed Tata Steel, Tata Steel, you
can spell it off here,
I have given the same in JSPL also, this
resistance of 1218,
if this is support, sorry support, this was the first
resistance  It was there but now it took support at the same point
in the race, this is the current
support on the stock, so the current support is
of 1220, so below that at 1218 you should
put a stop loss of 1234 on Tata Steel,
1213, 1205, 1190, for these three targets
in Tata Steel, tomorrow you have to select metal
stocks, you will always do it from here, I
always tell you and I am
saying continuously from last week that metal stocks, from
here I have invested money in Shell Metals, first NT Agri
Chemical, you will
make money, so here the fifth one which is behind medicine,
press his eyes, Bajaj Auto, so if
you want to buy in Bajaj Auto BPCL, then play the
top labels for
Activist
3700, if this system works above 3700 then only
you should buy, for intraday
put a stop loss of 3714, 3768,
so whatever price you have told Tata Motors,
you will see its movement in auto stocks
Very good, there was a bullish trend today, so tomorrow if Bajaj
Auto remains at the level of 7676 and
sustains, then you
can also see 3811 tomorrow, so
you will see a very good momentum in intraday, and you
must add
these 5 top stocks to your list. Now let's talk about
how this bangal can perform, half of
7676 will be a clear level for you to buy,
for intraday also it will be 760 because there will be a
bullish trend only above 760, if there is
no color laptop then avoid very straight,
anything can happen in the chemical market,
most of the conditions are that the market will again
gap down tomorrow, develop here at
lower levels and the market will do this, so
if ICICI Bank does not go down then
test for buying at 760, at that
time stoploss will be 755 for the
target 763 7603, tomorrow you will
see a very good momentum in intraday if on the
dance side, suppose 740 740, if you call
back then  For the target of 720, there will be a
flood in the bank from the neck, go for the shot, invest
in the bank with this but work on the words,
below 740,
above 760, you have to buy in it, so
I have told you the words of both ups and downs, the
rest is up to you, then
this money in the display will remain regularly, we people will also
download the office,
definitely subscribe to the channel because
on the i button you will find some such videos in which
I have also tried to give you learning,
Vikas, this is a channel, here you get
both of them together, so here guys, this is all the
complete update for today, you will get it
in tomorrow's next video
[Music]